Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
1960-2005
VRC 1800
Yale University Arts Library
30
180 boxes in 30 containers
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of the arts of China of all periods, pre-historic to the present. Includes architecture, painting, sculpture, calligraphy, bronzes and other metalwork, ceramics, ivory, jade, lacquer, textiles, rugs, and tapestry. For works from the Republican period to the present, identification information is given in Pinyin Romanization (unless otherwise cross-referenced). For earlier works, Wade-Giles Romanization is used.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of the arts of China of all periods, pre-historic to the present. Includes architecture, painting, sculpture, calligraphy, bronzes and other metalwork, ceramics, ivory, jade, lacquer, textiles, rugs, and tapestry. For works from the Republican period to the present, identification information is given in Pinyin Romanization (unless otherwise cross-referenced). For earlier works, Wade-Giles Romanization is used.
Arrangement
Arranged by medium. Further sub-divided by chronological period or location, and if known, by artist name.
Arts -- China; Slides; Reproductions
- Architecture (Box 1)
  General
  [Slide box 1]
  - General (Box 1)
    - Architectural Models (Box 1)
    - Bridges (Box 1)
    - Construction (Box 1)
    - Houses (Box 1)
      - Yin Yu Tang, House at Peabody Museum (Salem, MA) (Box 1)
    - Landscape (Box 1)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 1-2] (Box 1)
      - Great Wall [Slide box 2] (Box 1)
      - Kuilin Mountains (Box 1)
      - Moon Hill (Box 1)
      - Mt. Huangshan (Yellow Mountain) (Box 1)
      - Mt. Lu (Lushan Mountain) (Box 1)
    - Plans and Reconstructions (Box 1)
  - Prehistoric (Box 1)
    - Pan-p'o (Banpo) (Box 1)
  - Cities and Sites (Box 1)
    - Various (Box 1)
    - Anching [Slide box 3] (Box 1)
    - Anyang (Henan Province) (Box 1)
      - Tomb of Fu Hao (Box 1)
      - Wuguan Village (Box 1)
    - Deng feng, Henan (Box 1)
    - Guangzhou, Guangdong (Box 1)
    - Canton (Box 1)
    - Changsha (Hunan Province) (Box 1)
      - Mawangdui Tombs (W. Han) (Box 1)
    - Chao-Hsien (Box 1)
    - Chengde (Box 1)
    - Ch'eng-tu, Szechuan (Box 1)
    - Chia-Shan (Box 1)
    - Chia-Hua Shan (Box 1)
    - Datong (Shanxi) (Box 1)
      - Huayuan Temple (Box 1)
      - Tomb of Sima Jinlong [Slide box 4] (Box 1)
    - Hangchou (Box 1)
    - Hui-chou (Box 1)
    - Jiaohe City, Xinjiang (Box 1)
    - Khara Khorum (Box 1)
    - Kaskan, Sinkiang (Box 1)
    - Kuei-lin, Kwangsi (Box 1)
    - Leshan (Sichuan) (Box 1)
      - Mahao Tombs (E. Han) (Box 1)
    - Licheng, Shandong (Box 1)
    - Lo-Yang (Box 1)
    - Mai Chi Shan (Box 1)
    - Mancheng (Hebei) (Box 1)
      - Dou Wan Tomb (Box 1)
      - Liu Sheng Tomb (Box 1)
    - Mount Emei, Szechuan (Box 1)
    - Nanking [Slide box 5] (Box 1)
    - Nankow Pass (Box 1)
    - Ningbo, Zhejiang (Box 1)
    - Shaanxi Province (Box 1)
      - Maoling Mausoleum (W. Han) (Box 1)
      - Qianling Mausoleum (Tang) (Box 1)
      - Qinshi Huangdi Mausoleum, Shaanxi (Box 1)
        - Tomb (Box 1)
        - Excavation (Box 1)
        - Bronze figures (Box 1)
        - Terra cotta figures [Slide boxes 5-6] (Box 1)
      - Xianling Mausoleum (Tang) [Slide box 6] (Box 1)
      - Zhaoling Mausoleum (Tang) (Box 1)
    - Peking (Box 1)
      - Various Titles (Box 1)
      - Plans (Box 1)
      - General Views [Slide boxes 6-7] (Box 1)
      - Ming Tombs [Slide box 7] (Box 2)
      - Forbidden City (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Plans (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Views (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Gates (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Halls [Slide box 8] (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Imperial Gardens (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Palace Museum (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Palaces… (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Terraces and Rooftops (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Walls (Box 2)
        - Forbidden City Yang Hsin-Tien (Box 2)
        - Summer Palace (Box 2)
        - Temple of Heaven [Slide box 9] (Box 2)
        - Yuang Ming Yuan (Box 2)
    - Pingyao, Shanxi (Box 2)
    - Quanzhou, Fujian (Box 2)
    - Ruicheng, Shanxi (Box 2)
    - Shangdu (Box 2)
    - Shanghai (Box 2)
    - Shanxi Province (Box 2)
    - Shenyang (Box 2)
    - Sichuan Province (Box 2)
    - Sui Xian (Hubei) (Box 2)
    - Sian, Shensi (Xi'an, Shanxi) (Box 2)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 9-10] (Box 2)
      - General Views [Slide box 10] (Box 2)
      - Afang Palce Xi'an (Box 2)
        - Hanyan Hall (Box 2)
        - Nine Dragon Pond (Box 2)
        - Tzu-en Temple and Big Wild Goose Pagoda (Ta-yen T'a) (Box 2)
      - Xianyang Palace, Xi'an (Box 2)
    - Suchow (Box 2)
      - Various Titles (Box 2)
      - General Views (Box 2)
      - Chia-Ting [Slide boxes 10-11] (Box 2)
      - Cho-Cheng Yuan [Slide box 11] (Box 2)
      - Liu Yuan Gardens (Box 2)
      - Surging Wave Pavilion (Box 2)
      - Shin-Tzu Lin (Box 2)
      - Tiger Hill (Box 2)
      - Wang Shin-Yuan (Box 2)
    - Taigu, Shanxi (Box 2)
    - Taiyuan, Shanxi (Box 2)
    - Wutaishan, Shanxi (Box 2)
      - Various Titles (Box 2)
      - Nanchan Monastery (Box 2)
    - Yingxian, Shanxi [Slide box 12] (Box 2)
    - Ying Hsien, Shansi (Box 2)
    - Zhongshan Royal Tombs (War. States) (Box 2)
- Arms & Armor (Box 2)
  - Arms & Armor (Box 2)
- Calligraphy (Box 2)
  - Various Titles (Box 2)
  - Shang dynasty, ca. 1500-1030 BCE (Box 2)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 2)
  - Ch'in dynasty, 221-207 BCE (Box 2)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE (Box 2)
  - Six Dynasties, 221-581 (Box 2)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 2)
    - Known Artists (Box 2)
      - Various Titles (Box 2)
      - Wang Hsi-Chih, 307-365? [Slide box 13] (Box 3)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 3)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 3)
    - Known Artists (Box 3)
      - Various Titles (Box 3)
      - Chang Hsu (Box 3)
      - Ch'u Sui-Liang, 596-658 (Box 3)
      - Emperor Ming-Huang, 685-762 (Box 3)
      - Emperor T'ai-Tsung, 598-649 (Box 3)
      - Ho Chih-Chang (Box 3)
      - Hsuan-Tsung, 685-762 (Box 3)
      - Hsu Hao (Box 3)
      - Hsun Ouyang (Box 3)
      - Huai-Su [Slide boxes 13-14] (Box 3)
      - Li Po, 701-762 [Slide box 14] (Box 3)
      - Liu Chien-Chih (Box 3)
      - Pu Tien-Shou (Box 3)
      - Sun Kuo-T'ing, 648-703? (Box 3)
      - Yen Chen-Ch'ing, 709-785 (Box 3)
      - Yu Shih-Nan, 558-638 (Box 3)
  - Five Dynasties, 907-960 (Box 3)
    - Various Titles (Box 3)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 3)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 3)
    - Known Artists (Box 3)
      - Various Titles (Box 3)
      - Chang Chi-Chih, 1186-1266 (Box 3)
      - Chao Meng-Chien, 1199-1267 (Box 3)
      - Huang T'ing-Chien, 1045-1105 (Box 3)
      - Hui-Tsung, 1082-1126 [Slide box 15] (Box 3)
      - Kao-Tsung, 1107-1187 (Box 3)
      - Mi Fei, 1051-1107 (Box 3)
      - Su Shih, 1036-1101 (Box 3)
      - Yeh-Lu Ch'u-Ts'ai, 1190-1244 (Box 3)
  - Yuan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 3)
    - Known Artists (Box 3)
      - Various Titles (Box 3)
      - Chang Yu, 1275-1348 (Box 3)
      - Chao Meng-Fu, 1254-1322 [Slide boxes 15-16] (Box 3)
      - Feng Tzu-Chen, 1257-after 1327 [Slide box 16] (Box 3)
      - K'ang-Li Nao-Nao, 1295-1345 (Box 3)
      - K'o Chiu-Ssu, 1290-1343 (Box 3)
      - Kuo Pi, 1280-1335 (Box 3)
      - Shu Hsien-Yu, 1256-1301 (Box 3)
      - Sung K'e (Box 3)
      - Yang Wei-Chen, 1296-1370 (Box 3)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 3)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 3)
    - Known Artists (Box 3)
      - Chang Ch'ien-Fu, ac. 1640 (Box 3)
      - Chang Jui-T'u, ?-after 1640 (Box 3)
      - Chang Pi, 1425-1487 (Box 3)
      - Chao Huan-Kuang, 1559-1625 (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Chi-ju, 1558-1639 (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Hsien-Chang, 1428-1500 (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Hung-Shou, 1599-1652 (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Pi (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Shun, 1483-1544 [Slide box 17] (Box 3)
      - Ch'en Yuan-Su (Box 3)
      - Chin Shih, ac. 1440-1470 (Box 3)
      - Chou T'ien-Ch'iu, 1514-1595 (Box 3)
      - Chu Yun-Ming, 1460-152 (Box 3)
        - Various Titles (Box 3)
        - Coll. Hou Chen Shang Chai (Box 3)
        - New Fairfield, CT (Box 3)
          - Various Titles (Box 3)
          - Autumn Meditations (Box 3)
        - New York (Box 3)
          - Various Titles (Box 3)
          - Orchid Flower Song (Box 3)
          - Prose Poem on Fishing (Box 3)
        - Princeton (Box 3)
          - Various Titles (Box 3)
          - Poem, 1519 (Box 3)
      - Fa Jo-Chen, 1613-1696 (Box 3)
      - Hai Jui, 1514-1587 (Box 3)
      - Hsiang Sheng-Mo, 1595-1658 (Box 3)
      - Hsing T'ung, 1551-1612 (Box 3)
      - Hsu Hung-Chi [Slide box 18] (Box 3)
      - Hsu Lin, 1490-1548 (Box 3)
      - Hsu Wei, 1521-1593 (Box 3)
      - Li Tung-Yang (Box 3)
      - Liu Chueh, 1410-1472 (Box 3)
      - Mo Shih-Lung, d. 1587 (Box 3)
      - Mo Yun-Ch'ing, d. 1582 (Box 3)
      - Ni Yuan-Lu, 1583-1644 (Box 3)
      - P'u-Ho, 1593-1683 (Box 3)
      - Shen Chou, 1427-1509 (Box 3)
      - Shen Ts'an, 1379-1453 (Box 3)
      - Shen Tu, 1357-1434 (Box 3)
      - Shih K'o-Fa, 1602-1645 (Box 3)
      - Sung K'o, 1327-1387 (Box 3)
      - T'ang Yin, 1470-1524 (Box 3)
      - Tung Ch'i-Ch'ang, 1555-1636 (Box 3)
      - Wang Ao, 1450-1524 (Box 3)
      - Wang Ch'ung, 1494-1533 (Box 3)
      - Wang Ku-Hsiang, 1501-1568 (Box 3)
      - Wang Shou-Jen (Box 3)
      - Wang To, 1592-1652 (Box 3)
      - Wang Wen, 1497-1576 [Slide box 19] (Box 4)
      - Wen Cheng-Ming, 1574-1648 (Box 4)
        - Various Titles (Box 4)
        - Coll. Wang HC Weng (Box 4)
        - Coll. Mr. and Mrs. Hans Frankel (Box 4)
      - Wen P'eng, 1498-1573 (Box 4)
      - Wu I, 1472-1519 (Box 4)
      - Wu K'uan, 1436-1504 (Box 4)
      - Yao Shou, 1423-1495 (Box 4)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 4)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 4)
    - Known Artists (Box 4)
      - Various Titles (Box 4)
      - Chang Chao, 1691-1745 (Box 4)
      - Cheng Hsieh, 1693-1765 (Box 4)
      - Ch'ien Feng, 1740-1795 (Box 4)
      - Ch'en-Lung, 1711-1799 (Box 4)
      - Chin Nung, 1687-1764 (Box 4)
        - Various Titles (Box 4)
        - New York (Box 4)
      - Fu Shan, 1607-1684 (Box 4)
      - Ho Shao-Chi, 1799-1873 (Box 4)
      - Hua Yen, 1682-1765 (Box 4)
      - Huang Shen (Box 4)
      - I Ping-Shou, 1754-1815 (Box 4)
      - Kao Feng-Han, 1683-1748 (Box 4)
      - K'ang Yu-Wei, 1858-1927 (Box 4)
      - Kung Hsien, c. 1620-1689 [Slide box 20] (Box 4)
      - Li Shan, 1711-1762 (Box 4)
      - Liang Ch'ing-Piao, 1620-1691 (Box 4)
      - Liu Yung, 1719-1804 (Box 4)
      - Pa-Ta Shan-Jen, 1626-1705 (Box 4)
      - Shin T'ao, 1641-c.1720 (Box 4)
      - Ta-Shou, 1791-1858 (Box 4)
      - Teng Shih-Ju, 1743-1805 (Box 4)
      - Tso Tsung-T'ang, 1812-1885 (Box 4)
      - Wang Shih-Chen, 1686-1759 (Box 4)
      - Wang Shih-Min, 1592-1680 (Box 4)
      - Weng T'ung-Ho, 1830-1904 (Box 4)
      - Wu Changshuo, 1844-1927 (Box 4)
      - Wu Ta-Ch'eng, 1835-1902 (Box 4)
      - Yang I-Sun, 1813-1881 (Box 4)
      - Yang Shou-Ching, 1839-1915 (Box 4)
      - Yu Yueh, 1821-1906 (Box 4)
  - Republic, 1912- (Box 4)
- Ceramics (Box 4)
  - General [Slide boxes 20-21] (Box 4)
  - Prehistoric, -ca. 1500 BCE [Slide box 21] (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
    - Sites (Box 4)
      - Various titles (Box 4)
      - Kan-Ku (Box 4)
      - Lan-Chou (Box 4)
      - Ma-Ch'ang (Box 4)
      - Ma-Chia-Yao (Box 4)
      - Miao-Ti-Kou (Box 4)
      - Pan-P'o (Box 4)
      - Pan-Shan (Box 4)
      - P'ei-Hsien [Slide box 22] (Box 4)
      - Wei-Fang (Box 4)
      - Yang-Shao (Box 4)
  - Shang dynasty, ca. 1550-1030 BCE (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
    - Erh-Li-T'ou (Box 4)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE [Slide box 23] (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
  - Six Dynasties, 221-581 (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
    - Green-glazed ware (Box 4)
  - Sui dynasty, 581-618 (Box 4)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 23-24] (Box 4)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 4)
    - Various Titles (Box 4)
    - Celadon ware (Box 4)
    - Huang-tao ware (Box 4)
    - Lead-glazed ware (Box 4)
    - Three-color glazed ware (Box 4)
    - Underglazed ware (Box 4)
  - Five Dynasties, 907-960 [Slide box 25] (Box 5)
    - Various Titles (Box 5)
  - Liao dynasty, 907-1125 (Box 5)
    - Various Titles (Box 5)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 5)
    - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Black/brown ware (Box 5)
    - Celadon ware (Box 5)
    - Ch'ing-pai ware (Box 5)
    - Chun ware [Slide boxes 25-26] (Box 5)
    - Ju ware [Slide box 26] (Box 5)
    - Kuan ware (Box 5)
    - Ting ware (Box 5)
    - Tz'u-chou ware (Box 5)
  - Yuan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 5)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 26-27] (Box 5)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 [Slide box 27] (Box 5)
    - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Enamelled ware (Box 5)
    - Monochrome ware [Slide box 27-28] (Box 5)
    - Underglazed general ware [Slide box 28-29] (Box 5)
    - Underglazed red and white [Slide box 29] (Box 5)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 5)
    - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Enamelled ware [Slide box 29-30] (Box 5)
    - Monochrome ware [Slide box 30] (Box 5)
    - Underglazed ware (Box 5)
- Glass (Box 5)
  - Various Titles (Box 5)
- Enamel (Box 5)
  - Various Titles (Box 5)
- Furniture (Box 6)
  [Slide box 31]
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
- Implements (Pre-Historic) (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
- Jade (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Prehistoric, -ca. 1550 BCE (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Shang dynasty, ca. 1550-1030 BCE (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
    - Early Chou (Box 6)
    - Late Chou (Box 6)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE [Slide box 32] (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
    - Tomb of Nanyue King (Box 6)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Yuan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
- Jewelry (Box 6)
- Lacquer (Box 6)
  [Slide box 33]
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Yuan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
- Metals (Box 6)
  - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - Prehistoric, -ca. 1550 BCE (Box 6)
  - Shang dynasty, ca. 1550-1030 BCE [Slide box 34] (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
    - Axes (Box 6)
    - Chia (Box 6)
    - Chih (Box 6)
    - Chueh (Box 6)
    - Fang-I (Box 6)
    - Huo (Box 6)
    - Jia (Box 6)
    - Ku (Box 6)
    - Kuang [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
    - Kuei (Box 6)
    - Lei (Box 6)
    - Li (Box 6)
    - P'an (Box 6)
    - Ting (Box 6)
    - Tsun (Box 6)
    - Yu (Box 6)
  - Yin Chou (Box 6)
  - Early Chou (Box 6)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 35-36] (Box 6)
    - Fang-I [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
    - Ho (Box 6)
    - Hu (Huo) (Box 6)
    - Kuang (Box 6)
    - Kuei (Box 6)
    - Ting (Box 6)
    - Yu (Box 6)
  - Middle Chou (Box 6)
  - Late Chou (Box 6)
    - Various Titles [Slide box 36-37] (Box 6–7)
    - Bells [Slide box 37] (Box 7)
    - Hu (Box 7)
    - Mirror (Box 7)
  - Ch'in dynasty, 221-207 BCE (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Hsi Tsun (Box 7)
    - Hu (Box 7)
    - Lamps (Box 7)
    - Lien (Box 7)
    - Mirrors (Box 7)
    - Po-Shan (Box 7)
  - Six Dynasties, 221-581 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 37-38] (Box 7)
    - Bowls [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
    - Mirrors (Box 7)
      - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Famen Temple Crypt, Xian (Box 7)
  - Liao dynasty, 907-1125 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
- Tapestry (Box 7)
  - Various Titles (Box 7)
- Textiles (Box 7)
  - Various Titles [Slide boxes 38-39] (Box 7)
- Painting (Box 7)
  [Slide box 39]
  - General (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - European Influences (Box 7)
    - Erotic Art (Box 7)
    - Imperial Portraits (Box 7)
      - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - Song (Sung) Dynasty (Box 7)
      - Yuan Dynasty (Box 7)
      - Ming Dynasty [Slide boxes 39-40] (Box 7)
      - Qing (Ch'ing) Dynasty [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
  - Chou dynasty, 1030-222 BCE (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Ch'u Silk Manuscript (Box 7)
  - Han dynasty, 206 BCE-220 CE (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Boston Tile (Box 7)
    - Loyang Area Tombs (Box 7)
    - Loyang Tombs Tomb 61 [Slide boxes 40-41] (Box 7)
    - Ma-Wang-Tui Tombs [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
    - Mi-Hsien Model House, Ceramic (Box 7)
    - Mi-Hisen Tomb (Box 7)
    - Wang-Tu Tomb #1 (Box 7)
    - Ying-Yang Model House, Ceramic (Box 7)
  - Six Dynasties, 221-581 [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
    - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Tiles (Box 7)
      - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - Teng-Hsien Tiles (Box 7)
    - Tombs (Box 7)
      - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - Chia-Yu-Kuan (Box 7)
      - Dao Gui Tomb (N. Qi) (Box 7)
      - Dong Shou Tomb (E. Jin) (Box 7)
      - Lou Rui Tomb (N. Qi) (Box 7)
    - Ku K'ai-Chih, 344-406 (Box 7)
      - Cities (Box 7)
        - Various Titles (Box 7)
        - Liaoning (Box 7)
        - Peking (Box 7)
          - Nymph of the Lo River (Box 7)
          - Admonitions, details (Box 7)
        - London [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
          - Various Titles (Box 8)
          - Admonitions of the Court Instructress (Box 8)
        - Washington (Box 8)
          - Nymph of the Lo River (Box 8)
  - Sui dynasty, 581-618 (Box 8)
    - Chan Tzu-Ch-ien, c. 550-618 (Box 8)
      - Traveling in Spring (Spring Outing) (Box 8)
  - T'ang dynasty, 618-906 (Box 8)
    - Various Titles (Box 8)
    - Emperor Ming-Huang's Journey to Shu (Box 8)
    - Hokke Mandara [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
    - Horsemen (Box 8)
    - Snow Landscape (Box 8)
    - The Great Yü Stemming the Flood (Box 8)
    - Tombs and Caves (Box 8)
      - Various Titles (Box 8)
      - Chang-Huai Tomb (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Mounted Huntsmen (Box 8)
        - Rocks, Trees and Bamboo: details (Box 8)
        - Women in Garden (Box 8)
      - I-Te Tomb (Box 8)
      - Yung-T'ai Tomb [Slide boxes 44-45] (Box 8)
    - Known Artists [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
      - Chang Hsuan, c. 750 (Box 8)
      - Ch'en Hung (Box 8)
      - Chang Seng-yu (Box 8)
      - Chou Fang, c. 780-810 (Box 8)
        - Cities (Box 8)
          - Various Titles (Box 8)
          - Liaoning (Box 8)
          - Peking (Box 8)
            - Handscroll (Court Ladies) (Box 8)
          - Washington (Box 8)
            - Ladies Playing Double-Sixes (Box 8)
      - Han Huang, 723-789 (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Wen-Yuan T'u (Box 8)
      - Han Kan, ac. 742-756 (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Horses Led By Grooms (Box 8)
        - Monkeys & Horses (Box 8)
        - Two Horses & a Groom (Box 8)
      - Li Chao-Tao, ac. 670-730 [Slide box 46] (Box 8)
      - Li Chen (Box 8)
      - Li Ssu-Hsün, 651-716 (Box 8)
      - Lu Hung, ac. 700-725 (Box 8)
      - Lu Leng-Chia, 8th century (Box 8)
        - Six Lohans Album (Box 8)
      - Tiao Kuang-Yin (Box 8)
      - Wang Wei, 699-759 (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Wang Ch'uan T'u copies (Box 8)
        - Wang Ch'uan T'u rubbings (Box 8)
        - Clearing After the Snowfall (Box 8)
          - Cities (Box 8)
            - Kyoto (Box 8)
            - Honolulu (Box 8)
      - Wei-Ch'in I-Sung, 7th cent [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
      - Wu Tao-Tzu, ac. 720-760 (Box 8)
      - Yang Sheng (Box 8)
      - Yen Li-Pen (Box 8)
        - Cities (Box 8)
          - Boston (Box 8)
            - 13 Emperors (Box 8)
          - Peking (Box 8)
          - Taipei (Box 8)
          - Various Titles (Box 8)
          - Foreign Envoy with Tribute Bearers (Box 8)
          - Hsiao I Seizes the Lan-T'ing Calligraphy (Box 8)
  - Five Dynasties, 907-960 (Box 8)
    - Various Titles (Box 8)
    - Retreats in the Spring Hills (Box 8)
    - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 8)
      - Various Titles (Box 8)
      - Deer among Red Maples (Box 8)
      - Deer in Autumn Forest (Box 8)
      - Palace Concert (Box 8)
    - Known Artists [Slide box 48] (Box 8)
      - Chang Yüan (Box 8)
      - Chao Kan (Box 8)
        - Early Snow on the River (Box 8)
      - Chao Yen (Box 8)
      - Ching Hao, c. 900 (Box 8)
        - Landscape with Travelers (Box 8)
        - Mount Lu (Box 8)
      - Chou Wen-Chü (Box 8)
      - Hsü Hsi, c. 961-975 (Box 8)
        - Cities (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Shanghai (Box 8)
      - Hu Huai (Box 8)
      - Huang Ch'uan, c. 900-965 (Box 8)
      - Ku Hung-Chung, c. 943-960 [Slide box 49] (Box 9)
        - Night Entertainment of Han His-Tsai (Box 9)
          - Details (Box 9)
      - Kuan Hsiu, 832-912 (Box 9)
      - Kuan T'ung, c. 907-923 (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Autumn Mountains at Dusk (Box 9)
        - Travelers in the Mountains (Box 9)
        - Waiting to Cross a Mountain Stream (Box 9)
      - Kuo Chung-Shu, c. 910-976 [Slide boxes 49-50] (Box 9)
      - Li Sheng, ac. c. 908-925 [Slide box 50] (Box 9)
      - Li Tsan-Hua, c. 900-950 (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Nomads Bringing a White Horse for Tribute (Box 9)
      - Liu Tao-Shih (Box 9)
      - Shi K'o (Box 9)
      - Tung Yüan, d. 962 (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Cities (Box 9)
          - Hyogo (Box 9)
          - Peking (Box 9)
          - Shanghai (Box 9)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 9)
            - Inhabitants of Lung-Su (Box 9)
            - Taoist Temple in the Mountains (Box 9)
      - Wei Hsien, 10th century (Box 9)
        - Flour Mill (Box 9)
        - Kao-shih t'u (Box 9)
      - Yuan Kao [Slide box 51] (Box 9)
  - Liao dynasty, 907-1125 (Box 9)
    - Various Titles (Box 9)
    - Liao Tombs (Box 9)
    - Ch'ing-Ling (Box 9)
  - Sung dynasty, 960-1279 (Box 9)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 9)
      - Various Titles (Box 9)
      - Boston (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Clear Weather in the Valley [Slide box 52] (Box 9)
        - Mist Over the Valley (Box 9)
      - Cleveland (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Bird on a Flowering Branch (Box 9)
        - Magpies and Wild Rabbits (Box 9)
        - Amitabha with Two Attendants (Box 9)
        - Bodhidharma Meditating Facing a Cliff (Box 9)
        - Ladies of the Court (Box 9)
        - One Hundred Children at Play (Box 9)
        - Streams and Mountains Without End (Box 9)
      - Kansas City (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Chao Yu's Pacification of Barbarians South of Lu (Box 9)
        - Traveling Amid Rivers and Mountains (Box 9)
      - Kyoto (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
      - Liaoning [Slide box 53] (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
      - Nanking (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
      - New York (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Bird on Loquat Tree (Box 9)
        - Birds Circling (Box 9)
        - Boating by Willow Bank (Box 9)
        - Conversation in a Cave (Box 9)